Hey.
Hi.
Who wants French toast?
Oh, I'll have some.
Me, too.
Eggs and milk
in the fridge. Thanks.
Ow!
What's the matter, honey?
My hand feels weird.
I guess it's because
I'm engaged!
How long before
that starts getting annoying?
Starts?
So, let's actually get started
on the wedding plans.
Okay.
Already?
Yeah, we got a lot to do.
We got to think about flowers,
the caterers, the music.
I have thoughts on that.
Oh, Chandler, too many cooks.
Take it from me. As the groom
all you have to do is show up
and try to say the right name.
Okay.
What in God's name is that?
Oh, my God.
The wedding book?
I haven't seen that
since the fourth grade.
Monica:
This baby has
got everything.
Take, you know,
locations, for instance:
first organized alphabetically,
then geographically
then by square footage.
That is so smart.
( softly ):
Break it off.
( coughs ):
Break it off now.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's DOA ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been your day ♪
♪ Your week, your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
And that should
conclusively prove
that I had the idea
for Jurassic Park first.
Now, let's...
Hey, Ross.
Phoebe, oh, my God.
What are you doing here?
I need to talk to you.
It's pretty urgent.
It's about Monica
and Chandler.
Oh, my God.
Of course.
Would you please
excuse me for a moment?
Do you know
each other's hometowns?
Why don't you...?
What's going on?
Well, not much, but
I was just thinking
that since those guys
just got engaged
that maybe it'd
be nice if they had
some privacy, you know?
So, could I just
move in with you
for a couple days?
Um, okay. Yeah, sure
but what's wrong
with Monica and Chandler?
Nothing. Why?
Phoebe, you said it was urgent.
Oh, yeah, it is. I'm
going to the movies
and it starts in,
like, five minutes.
Do you realize
I have a classroom
full of students?
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm so rude.
Does anyone want to come
to the movies?
All right, I haven't cleared
the budget with my parents yet
but tell me how
this is for music.
Okay.
A string quartet
for the processional
a jazz trio
for cocktails
the Bay City Rollers
for dancing... wait.
That was for my
sixth-grade wedding.
Well, you couldn't
get them, anyway.
I mean, Ian doesn't even
play anymore and Derek...
Well, Derek is a name
I shouldn't know.
Hey, Mon, do you have
another pillow?
You know,
something a little snugglier?
Why are you napping over here
instead of over at your place?
The duck.
What? The duck?
What the hell did
the damn duck do now?
Uh, well, he did not
get sick somewhere in there
and it was immediately found
and properly cleaned up.
Now do I get
to look at this book
or is it just for people
who are actually involved
in the wedding?
Of course
you can look at it.
Yeah, I want
your opinion, too.
Okay.
Here you go.
What do you think
about centerpieces?
Centerpieces.
Yeah.
Roses... or lilies?
Definitely roses.
Well, I just think they're
a little bit more weddingy.
But lilies are the clear choice.
Oh, my God.
It's like one mind.
Uh-huh.
Guys, guys...
you got to let me nap.
I'm going to get cranky.
Joey, there is a perfectly
good couch across the hall.
Yes, it is perfectly good...
and it is not one of the places
the duck got sick.
What?
All right, I'm going to go.
Joey
what did the duck do?
I don't know, but
he did not eat
your face cream.
Hey, little buddy.
How you feeling? Ah!
What the hell
is in that face cream?
That's so soft.
Pillowcases.
Oh, yeah...
Oh, oh... oh...
What the...?
"Zelda looked at
the chimney sweep.
Her father, the vicar..."
Vicar? Hmm.
"...wouldn't be home for hours.
"Her loins were burning.
"She threw caution to the wind
and reached out
and grabbed his..."
Whoa!
Whoa.
This is a dirty book.
Uh, Phoebe?
( deep, sultry voice ):
Oh, Ross, hi.
Phoebe, what
are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I'm with a client right now.
Phoebe!
Okay, let's talk outside.
Phoebe, you can't
massage people
in my apartment.
What's the big deal?
I did it
at Monica and Chandler's.
And they knew about it?
Okay, look, Ross,
what is this really about?
Look, this is my home
and I want to be able
to come and go whenever I want.
Okay, I will find
someplace else
to do the rest
of my appointments.
I just don't know
what the big deal is.
The big deal is, I don't want
naked, greasy strangers
in my apartment when I want
to kick back with a puzzle...
beer-- cold beer.
Hey.
Hey, Joey. What
are you doing?
Sweeping.
Why? Does it turn you on?
No.
Hmm...
What if I was, uh,
sweeping a chimney?
Joey, did you eat my face cream?
Where you going?
The vicar won't be home
for hours.
Joey... where did you
learn that word?
Where do you think...
Zelda?
( gasps )
You found my book?
Yeah, I did!
Joey, what-what
are you doing
going into my bedroom?
Okay, I'm sorry.
I went in there to take a nap
and I know I shouldn't have,
but you got porn.
Oh!
You... hey, you know what?
I don't care.
I'm not ashamed of my book.
There's nothing wrong with
a woman enjoying a little...
erotica.
It's just a healthy expression
of female sexuality
which, by the way, is something
that you will never understand.
You got porn.
( laughing )
( yells )
( knocking at door )
Hello.
Hi.
Is, uh, Phoebe here?
Uh, no, no.
Sh-she's out for the night.
Oh, great.
Can I... can I help you
with something?
Oh, I don't know.
Are you a masseur?
Yes, I am.
Great.
Dad?
Thank you so much.
I'll be back to
pick him up
in an hour.
So, Chandler, your parents
must have been thrilled
when you told them
you were engaged.
Oh, yeah, I should
probably call them.
I remember when we
first got engaged.
Oh, I don't think
I've ever heard
that story.
Dad, really,
you don't need...
Well, I had gotten Judy
pregnant.
I still
don't know
how that happened.
You don't know
how that happened?
Your dog thought my diaphragm
was a chew toy.
What a sweet story.
Well, at least
you're not
hearing it
for the first time at your
fifth-grade Halloween party.
What? They wanted a scary story.
( chuckling )
Anyway, we're really excited
about our wedding plans
and I guess pretty soon
we'll be making a big withdrawal
from the Monica wedding fund.
( Monica and Chandler chuckle)
Uh-oh.
What?
You tell her, Jack,
I can't do it.
You still have the Monica
wedding fund, don't you?
We have it.
Only now we call it
"the beach house."
I can't believe you spent
my wedding fund
on the beach house!
We're sorry, honey
but we just assumed
if you got married
after you turned 30,
you'd pay for it yourself.
You bought the beach house
when I was 23.
Which means you had
seven years of beach fun
and you can't put
a price on that, sweetie.
We really do feel bad
about this, though.
We started saving again
when you were dating Richard
but then that went to hell,
so we re-did the kitchen.
What about when
I started dating Chandler?
Well, it was Chandler.
We didn't think
he'd ever propose.
Clearly, I did not start
drinking enough
at the start of the meal.
( chuckling )
I can't believe it.
There is no money
for my wedding?
We might still have
some money
if your father hadn't thought
it was a good idea
to sell ice
over the Internet.
It seemed like such
a simple idea.
"Stupid," Jack.
The word is "stupid."
All right, enough.
I don't want to hear
about it anymore.
Good luck, Chandler.
Okay.
Now, I'm going to...
touch you.
Oh, that's soft.
I can't believe this.
Do you think
that your parents
can help pay for it?
I don't know.
My mother spent
most of her money
on her fourth wedding
and she's saving the rest
for her divorce.
And any extra cash my father has
he saves for his yearly trips
to... Dollywood.
Well, what happened at dinner?
My parents spent the money
for our wedding.
( gasps )
My God!
What did you order?
Wait, but... there's no money?
Well, this is terrible!
You guys are going to have
to get married in, like
a rec center.
Honey, it's
going to be okay.
No, no, it's not.
It's not going to be okay.
It sucks!
No swing band, no lilies...
No, you know what?
It's going to be okay.
I mean, you don't need
to have this...
rustic Italian feast, you know?
And-and you don't need
this custom-made, empire-waisted
duchess satin gown.
You can wear off-the-rack.
Look, it really is
going to be okay.
The important thing
is that we love each other
and that we're going
to get married.
Do you even understand
what "off-the-rack" means?
Look, why
don't you
just pay for it yourself?
How? I don't have
any money.
Well, I have some.
How much?
Well, close to...
Wow! Are you
kidding me?
Well, what?
How-how much is it?
It's enough
for wedding scenario "A."
( gasping ):
Really?
How great are you,
you little saver?!
I mean, the
amount you have is
exactly the budget
of my dream wedding.
Oh! You guys are so made
for each other.
Well, you're not suggesting
that we spend all of the money
on the wedding?
Uh, yeah!
Look... Mon, I've been saving
this money for six years
and I kind of had some of it
earmarked for the future
not just for a party.
Wow! Hello, Mr. Chandler.
Sweetie, this is the most
special day of our lives.
No, I realize that, honey
but I'm not going to spend
all the money on one party.
Honey, um, I-I love you...
( giggles )
...but, um, if you call our
wedding a "party" one more time
you may not get invited, okay?
Listen...
we can always earn
more money, okay
but we're only going
to get married once.
Look, I understand
but I have to put
my foot down, okay?
The answer is no.
You-you're going to have
to "put your foot down"?
Yes, I am.
Wow.
Money and a firm hand.
Finally a Chandler
I can get on board with.
Hi, Rach.
Joey.
Hey, Rach.
Do you smell smoke?
Uh-huh. I get it. Smoke, chimney
chimney sweep-- very funny.
Ha, ha.
No, no, no. I'm serious.
You don't smell it?
Something's on fire.
No, I don't smell anything.
Oh, you know what?
It's probably
just your burnin' loins.
Hey, what are you guys
talking about?
Nothing.
Hmm. Dang, this
coffee's cold.
Hey, Rach, do you mind
if I heat this up on your loins?
You know,
I cannot believe
you told him.
Joey...
So, I guess you bought that book
after we broke up, huh?
Uh-huh. Yeah, I did
because I wore out my first copy
when I was with you.
Oh, yeah, yeah?
Well, uh, when we were going out
I read tons of porno magazines!
Whassup?
Ross, how could you
do that to an old man?!
Excuse me, ladies.
I'm sorry?
My massage client,
Arthur?
His daughter called
and said that some guy
that worked for me
gave him a really
weird massage
this afternoon.
I gave him an extremely
professional massage.
He said you poked at him
with wooden spoons.
Well, okay, so it wasn't,
a-a traditional massage.
But I did give him acupressure
with a pair of chopsticks.
And, and, I gently exfoliated
him with-with a mop.
Well, he's never
coming back.
Okay, you just cost
me $80 a week!
Hey, you know what?
This is your fault.
You're the one who didn't move
his appointment.
Oh, it's my fault?
You didn't have to massage him.
You could've sent him away.
You could've not rolled
Tonka trucks
up and down his back!
He said he liked that!
Oh, you're right, you're right.
I'm sorry.
Dude...
What are you massaging
an old man for?
His daughter was hot.
Gotcha.
( door opens )
Hey.
Listen, um...
I've been thinking
and...
It's not fair for me to ask you
to spend all of your money
on our wedding.
I mean, you work... you work
really hard for that.
Yeah.
Well, you worked for that.
Look, I've thought
about it, too
and I'm sorry.
I think we should spend
all of the money
on the wedding.
You do?
Yeah, I'm putting
my foot down.
( chuckling )
Yeah, look.
When I proposed,
I told you
that I would do anything
to make you happy...
and if having the perfect
wedding makes you happy
then... then that's
what we're going to do.
You are so sweet.
Oh, but wait.
What about, what about
the future and stuff?
Ahh, forget about
the future and stuff.
So we only have two kids.
You know, we'll pick
our favorite
and that one will get
to go to college.
I mean, you've thought
about that?
Yeah.
How many kids
were we gonna have?
Uh, four: a boy,
twin girls,
and another boy.
What else
did you think about?
Well, stuff like
where we'd live.
You know,
like a small place
outside the city
where our kids could learn
to ride their bikes and stuff.
You know, we could have a cat
that had a bell on its collar
and we could hear it every time
it ran through
the little kitty door.
Of course, we'd have
an apartment over the garage
where Joey could grow old.
You know what?
I-I don't want a big,
fancy wedding.
Sure you do.
No.
I want everything
that you've just said.
I want a marriage.
You sure?
Mm-hmm.
I love you so much.
I love you.
Hey, listen, um
when you were talking
about our future
when you said cat,
but you meant dog, right?
Yeah, totally.
Oh, good.
Hello, Zelda.
Who are you supposed to be?
The vicar!
Do you even know
what a vicar is?
It's like a goalie, right?
Yeah.
Look, Joey, it's
enough, all right?
You're making these stupid jokes
and these sleazy innuendoes
and it's, I'm not...
It's just not funny anymore!
All right, I'm sorry.
Rach, I'm sorry.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Maybe I can make it up
to you by...
taking you roughly in the barn.
Aah!
All right, you know what?
That's it.
You want to do it?
Let's do it.
Huh?
That's right.
I want to do it with you.
Been trying to fight it
but you've just said
all the right things.
I-I-I did?
Yeah.
Oh, I've been waiting so long
to get on that body.
This body?
Yeah, that's right.
Come on, Joey.
Sex me up.
Hey, hey, you're
starting to sound like
the butcher's wife
there in chapter seven.
Oh, come on, now.
Don't keep me waiting.
Get those clothes off.
But I would keep
that helmet on
'cause you're in
for a rough ride.
I don't want to.
I'm scared.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]